I genuinely think these Zionists are like the worst, and I've had a lot of racist bullshit
in my comments, but here's Blendy. You are an absolute piece of filth. I hope you burn in hell,
and I really mean it. You have absolutely no idea what the Holocaust was, okay? When you compare
that to what is happening to Gaza, you have no idea what the Holocaust was. Otherwise, you would
not post such a disgusting video. No wonder your career fell off, did it? And all you have is
posting reels and videos, and you no longer get invited to events. Of the 20 million people died
in Europe during World War II and 6 million Jews during the Holocaust, and now you want to use
that word to compare it to Gaza. Well, Blendy, you have terrible grammar because you literally used
two, only two punctuation points in this video, and you have a terrible soul and spirit, and you
have no comprehension skills. To be clear, there were more Jewish people and Roma and black people
and gay people in Germany at the time, so the number is higher because there were more people
there. It doesn't mean that the intention wasn't the same. We can compare the Nachba of 1948 to
Kristallnacht, which is the night that the SS and the Nazis decided, okay, we're going to actually turn
this whole thing into something real. And from that night where they destroyed Jewish businesses,
they began putting stars on Jewish people to be able to mark them, okay? We know that Palestinians
are forced to carry cards and forced to be identified on a regular basis to make sure that
they are only using the resources that they're supposed to use and not that are available to
Jewish people. Genocide is not something that is just packaged up in a nice little box with a pretty
bow and looks the same every time. However, its intention is the same every time, and it is the
annihilation of a people. It is the ethnic cleansing. It is the destruction of their bodies. It is the
destruction of their histories. It is the destruction of their systems. It is the effort to take out
from the bottom everything that they have built up themselves onto. And we have seen that. We have seen
that in real time. So get off this internet and get a book or actually stay on this internet and follow
the Palestinian people who are showing you, who are displaying for you in real time, the effort to destroy
their existence and how many people like you, blendy, have made it your business to perpetuate the lie that
an entire people do not exist. And when you tell me that I don't know anything about the Holocaust, you are not
only disrespecting me, but you are disrespecting my sixth and seventh grade gifted teacher, Ms. Diana Lewis,
who made it her business to show us the true horrors of the Holocaust and to teach us that it wasn't just
the army. It was also the people, the people who allowed for this genocide to happen. Yes. And she taught us
so that we would grow up to be people who challenge when we see things like this happening. And so that we do not
become those people.